PERSONAL INFORMATION

Md Rezaul Islam



Address | House 62, Road 18, Sector 11, Uttara, Dhaka, BD 1230

Phone | +88 01738157678

E-Mail | rezabdt@gmail.com

Portfolio | http://rezabdt.github.io/

1 LinkedIn | https://www.linkedin.com/in/rezabdt/

Skype | rezabdt007

Gender: Male | Date Of Birth: 17/09/1991 | Nationality: Bangladeshi

CAREER SUMMARY

I'm a Digital Marketer. SEO, SMM & Web Development with Over 5 Years of Experience. Experienced with All Stages of The Marketing Cycle for Product Promotion & Also CMS Developer.

- 5 Years of Professional Experience with 10+ Years of Marketing skills
- Marketing Experience in Google Adwords, Facebook Ads, ASO
 & All Mainstream Social Media. Also Email Marketing.
- Analytical Skill to Understand Market.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Jun 2019 -Dec 2020

Digital Marketing Executive | Full Time

Alt Fix Ltd. | Baridhara DOSH, Dhaka, Bangladesh

Sales & Marketing | Image Post Production

Responsibilities:

- Digital Marketing
- Web Development & Maintenance
- Graphics Design

Oct 2017 - Present

Team Lead | Part-Time

WeblyWork | Lalmonirhat, Rangpur, Bangladesh

Sales & Marketing | Software & ITES

Responsibilities:

- Digital Marketing
- Android Development, Front-End & Back-End Development
- Leadership Team of 5
- Development & Maintaining Projects for Clients

Apr 2017 - May 2017

Lead Trainer | Contract

LEDP | Lalmonirhat, Rangpur, Bangladesh

Digital Marketing | Training Course

Responsibilities:

- Search Engine Optimization (SEO)
- Social Media Marketing (SMM)
- Email Marketing
- Freelancing Marketplace

July 2013 - Present Freelancer | Part-Time

Fiverr & Upwork | fiverr.com, upwork.com Sales & Marketing | Digital Marketing

Responsibilities:

Social Media Marketing (SMM)

Search Engine Optimization (SEO)

May 2010 – June 2013 Marketing Executive | Full Time

RangpurSource | Rangpur, Bangladesh

Sales & Marketing | Digital Marketing

Responsibilities:

Search Engine Optimization (SEO)

Social Media Marketing (SMM)

Email Marketing

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Jan 2010 - Dec 2012 Bachelor of Commerce (B.Com)

Business Studies | National University

Result | 2nd Division

Jan 2007 - Dec 2009 Higher Secondary Certificate (H.S.C)

Commerce | Lalmonirhat Govt. College, Lalmonirhat, Rangpur, Bangladesh

Result | GPA 3.00 out of 5.00

Jan 2005 - Dec 2006 Secondary School Certificate (S.S.C)

Science | Bangladesh Railway Children Park High School, Lalmonirhat, Rangpur,

Bangladesh

Result | GPA 3.94 out of 5.00

PERSONAL SKILLS

Mother Tongue(s)

English

Bangla

Other Language(s)

UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
Listening	Reading	Spoken interaction	Spoken production	
Average	Average	Average	Average	Average

Communication Skills

I have gathered good client communication skills during my various project life cycle.

Organizational / Managerial Skills

- Leadership Team of 5
- Project Management skills at a present organization.

Digital Skills

5	Digital Marketing	Web Development	Graphics Design	Apps Development	Problem Solving	
	EXPERT	AVERAGE	AVERAGE	BELOW	BELOW	

Learning and Earning Development Project, ICT Division Certifications

> Course: Digital Marketing Duration: 300 Hours

SEO, SMM, Email Marketing, Google Ads, Facebook Ads, ASO, Technical Skills

HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, WordPress, Joomla, Android Studio, Ads Networks, Photoshop, Illustrator, Premiere Pro, After Effect,

Domain, Hosting, Ubuntu Server.

Bangladesh | M&E Manager -References

Program Quality, SHOUHARDO

Md. Eyasin Ali Sarker | CARE

III Program

RAOWA Complex, VIP Road, Mohakhali, Dhaka-1206,

Bangladesh

Phone:+880-2-9889009, Ext 221 | Cell +880 1718595626 | email: eyasinali.sarker@care.org

Arman Hossain

Mobile Application Developer, Shakti Foundation,

Mirpur 1, Dhaka, Bangladesh Mobile: 01918-304040

Email:

armans.postbox@gmail.com

I do hereby declare that all the information given above is true to the best of my knowledge and belief.

Respectfully yours,

Md Rezaul Islam

Last Modified: 01 / 06 / 2021